Guide to the COLLECTION NAME HERE, YYYY-YYYY IBT0085
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Norman Kloke Papers
1965-2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0085
1 record center boxes Materials mainly dealing with the IBT 1996 Convention.
This collection contains materials collected by Norman Kloke. Most materials pertain to the 25th Convention of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The collection also contains files pertaining to Norman Kloke's activities as a Teamster.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by subject and chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Norman Kloke, 2017 (2017.049)
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials collected by Norman Kloke. Box 1 contains files from the 25th Convention of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Box 2 contains other materials collected by Norman Kloke, such as local Teamsters newspapers and personal correspondence.
Biographical / Historical
Norman Kloke is a longtime member of the International Brotherhood of Teamster. He served as a trustee of Local 554 for 12 years. Additionally, he served as the Recording Secretary and Business Agent for local 631. He served as an elected delegate to the 1996 and 2001 International Brotherhood of Teamsters Conventions. After retiring, he became a member of the Joint Council 41 Teamsters Retiree Association Las Vegas Branch.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transfered from IBT, 2017 (2017.049).
General
- 25th Convention Proceedings, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Committee Reports to the Teamsters 25th International Convention, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Constitution Adopted by the 24th Convention, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Construction Hand Book, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Elected Delegates- Not Certified List, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Financial Statements and Reports of the Independent Certified Public Accountant, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- General Presidents' Project Maintenance By Contract, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Hoffa Campaign Publicity, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Initial Credentials Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- List of No Raid Mutual Aid Pacts, ND (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Proposed Constitution and Bylaws, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Office of the Election Officer Memorandums, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Official Convention Call, ND (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Official List of Delegates, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Roadtrip: Retiree Planning Packet, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Proposals Submitted to the Constitution Committee by Ron Carey, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Southern Nevada Teamsters Retiree Association Business Card and Envelope (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Ritual of the Teamsters, ND (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 2nd Annual Crime Prevention Seminar, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Midwest Teamsters Newspapers, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Safety Program for the Fucinaro Excavating Company and Conreco Inc, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Omaha Labor Chronicle Newspaper, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Las Vegas Convention Magazine, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 631 Reporter, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Personal Files, 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)